Hello, friend, welcome back.
In this video, I want to discuss about another Caldbeck alternative as a that's okay here, I want
to do in this video to discuss about the promise, a promise.
So how that promise actually work, like, first of all, I want to do.
I simply won't be everything.
OK, I remove everything from this area, and here I want to add on the set.
Timeout seemed to set them on what I have already discussed about the things we do that will burn the
function right?
So this function, after the particular time, you can actually display some of the message like here,
I put that to the console.log here.
I named the high RDM, high RDM.
So this step of one of the masses after the two second, that will be displayed, right?
So here we have to do have to pass it like a three seconds for the three seconds.
That is a three thousand millisecond gap in the three second.
OK, so here after the three second that we display our high RDM message and I will look at the savon
now go directly to the refresh.
So after the three second now so successfully display art, this message, which is totally fine.
So now on to do I'll declare on the promise.
We will declare that will in the corner structure.
And here I take one of the promise, I promise, and I want to just declare the new promise so that
it was a promise, a promise.
So I simply load it.
And here that will be the callback function.
So that is a callback function.
And this function actually part two of this parameter one is the result that I return and address.
There is a parameter.
OK, so here you can see that is also display other result parameter and also outside of the parameter
as a result.
So first of all, to do until they meet, as a result, get a result and also another parameter and
then reject.
OK, reset reset.
So with this to have this parameter, how what exactly that will be the result.
Actually, this function worked for, we knew perfectly.
Get some of the data from your database, then that the result function will be executed.
And if there have any adult who is getting that data and see what it's getting that that I believe they
have any arrow, then our reset function will be executed.
OK.
So first of all, to do here, but I want to show you the live example I take out of the set timeout
and here you can use it as a function area.
So I use that as a function, our function functionality, I just simply declare, OK, I'll just simply
declare it.
And now I want to turn to this display.
One of the messages, OK, so one of the messages will be get that message.
If we get perfectly data, then we can actually display it with the result function.
So this resolve area here I want, then that would be done as a one.
OK.
And also after we start missing, we get this data.
I just make it there after a three second or two seconds, after two seconds till we get all of the
data.
So I simply added that our timeout in here.
So that is a timeout.
I simply load it and I hope you already know about it.
So here I am actually parsing that with the result function.
That is one that means if they have everything OK, even if it's perfectly good, is that if everything
OK, then that will be as a result.
And then if they have any arrow, they can display it with this redirect function, OK, then how it
can actually display, then we have to display it with the respect that is a risk.
And even with this reject area here, just simply click, OK.
Oh yeah.
So that is our arrow.
And then your message like here, hi, there.
Like there are some arrow.
So this type of one on the arrow, then that will be display.
So I hope you give someone the idea with this result.
If you want to a parcel tax taxes, well, we can pass it if they have any at all, you can pass it
with this result, and that will be your error message.
OK, so that is at our object.
So that is not the default object.
So we this or object, you can actually display all that your address, but your demand.
OK.
I hope you get some idea how that promises actually work.
So now if you want to print this data right now, you don't need this.
I simply remove it, OK?
I simply removed it.
And here that is the last one.
And after this, I want to turn the display over this variable that in the console console.log, there
is a console look and here I want to display our promise.
OK, so that is upgradable.
I simply load it.
So now what exactly should we do after that two seconds that should be displayed on the message right
now, if you look at save all now, if you go near the refresh now consistent display as it promises
as a painting.
OK, so here right now, it's actually all this total data and this display, depending.
So how can actually solve this issue?
So first of all, I want to discuss about that.
Our result?
OK, results here.
I wanted to close it and there is a resolve here.
From here, I pass on that one, right?
So if you want to access this function, there are the two methode as a then and cast method.
OK, so I show you like here.
I want to do one to access it.
So that will be as I just named to the promises.
And then then my thought, OK, so that is the map would seem to this then matter really are here.
On the function, I simply decline the function and whatever the result, if we get here, I want to
pass on the perimeter as a result.
OK, I passed one of the parameters as a result crate.
And now with this result, we can actually paint that missile to show that console.
Log into this console.log area here and deposit that result.
OK, sorry result.
So I simply pass this result to our everything.
OK, if they have perfectly good this data here, I pass on that one below, right?
So now if you want to access this resolved, then as I told you, there is a two method one is that
the method and the catch method for now with this their method here, I pass one on the function and
I give this our total data.
That means that is our result, right?
So here I pass one of the parameters, the result, I name it, as a result.
And now I simply lauded this result.
Now if you click the save all now you go because refresh now after that two second, it should be displayed
the one you can see.
It's now successfully this bloody one.
OK, fine.
I hope it is very much clear to you.
And now if you want to display that every sick message, then you can also display better here.
Want to make it as a reject function, according to the resistance mounted on to declare the error message.
So we declared declare that it must, as I have already discussed, a vote of the arrows.
And if this are, or what type of arrow do you want to display, you can display like I just make it
as, hi there, there have been some error.
OK, so this step up on the message now that will be displayed.
So if you want to access this restrict function, then you have to use it as it gets OK for the result.
You have to use that as a method and for the reject, you have to use that as it gets method.
Now let's do that work here after this.
After this, I wanted to declare another method OK, here I'll declare and the method I did not catch.
So there is a catch method.
So into this catch method or facsimile tool with them into the function or whatever the result I will
get, I make out or OK, this double barreled message.
I pass on the parameter.
And now on to do under display that is a console and then the console log on to parse that out.
OK, I simply pass it.
So here that is our reject.
And then here I pass on this gene value.
Now with this catch method that will be connected with our this is a function that will be disallowed.
This message not only is it as to save all.
And now if you go if you go, click on the refresh after the two second, OK, you can see snapshot
display as at or hi, there have something at or OK, I often it's very much clear to you.
And also here you can see display.
The total things right is display the total error and then that is the message.
So if you want to only display that message that in this message, then you can also display it, then
that will be the dot and then the message, OK, message.
That means that these are at object or on the property as a message, and I want to do have to declare
it now because I save all now.
That should be display only that message after the two second, yeah, because it's not successful display
only the message I unfriend you give someone the idea about that promise.
So is very much interactive.
One of the things I make that sure you understand it.
So thanks for watching.
I will see you in the next video.