Hello, friend, welcome back.
In this video, I want to discuss about how can dealing with multiple parameters?
I show you the life example, then that will be very interactive.
I simply will be everything.
And first of all, I want to do and declare two of these promises.
I hope you already know that is a variable I take on.
Namely, does a promise a promise one?
OK.
And then the two, I want to turn to declare this promise.
That is to declare that new and then promise.
I simply declare I'm here to do part two of this parameter, right?
And here there is a function with the function of the end 12:02.
This parameter one parameter will be as a result.
And also the parameter function will be as a result, right?
And how what exactly the result, what exactly that I reject.
I hope you already know about it.
If you get perfect data, then you can display with the result rather than if there are any add or we
can build it with this respect, right?
So simply take both of this.
And here I declare the array function.
OK.
That is the added function.
And now I want to declare on the set time out and this time down to declare the added function.
OK, that is our function and this function area here.
I want to do that every function and I want to run our result, get a result and enter this result variable
to pass one of the value as a one.
OK.
I simply pass one of the value of the one, and this one below will display our time out.
Time out will be added 2000 2000 millisecond.
OK, that is after that two.
Second that should we display other results?
One.
Right.
And also take another one I copied.
And then I pasted that will be as a promise to OK, you just simply name it as a promise to and then
that will be the result again.
And from here, I intended to pass it to value.
OK, so that is or it will be resolved by pass one.
And also in here, I pass that as a two.
So now if you want to display both of these, then what exactly you have to do, then that is a promise.
And then there is another matter the all method.
OK, so here we have to declare this all method and into this All-Nighter area.
I think that both of these with the added I have the two things that one is the promise promise one
and also the other one, the promise to promise to assembly.
Take both of these in here.
And then with this, then this then method into this the method.
I understand the pass on the result.
That means our response, OK, Balderas response.
And then do that with this added function, we decided to function, want to do and this played out
of his play or this console and then the console log into this console.log area on the display or who
used that under this blower?
This test data?
OK, here I have already get it.
I get both of these response data in all this parameter as a response.
And here I just simply painted.
OK.
And if they have any error, then what exactly you have to do?
We have to display it.
We don't get it right.
So that is all them.
And also that is another one as a catch.
So now I want to do two and also but use it, that is where the dock catch method, right?
That is a catch method seem to discuss properties that have any error, then that will be possible.
The error?
OK, but that name of that or and then they were at a function on the display, this arrow to the console
and then the console log.
I'm here to learn to parse this out.
OK.
I think at the point you already knew about it.
So now if you click on this, save, all right now, they have narrowed down the actual display to have
this dark back look at the refresh.
So after the two second tier inconsistent display or fast blue as a one and the other two, right?
So this ad agency, though, still perfectly displayed the one below two values.
So here I simply take as a one.
So you see this result here I pass one below and here there is another one as it developed.
So now if you want to display that error here, I have already loaded the catch.
But also with this catch method is to work with which one is that we work with respect, right?
So that is a risk.
And into the street, Victoria Island would be split on the message.
So if the display, then that would be the new and our outer object.
So that is our object.
And here what of the message you want to display?
Like, there have some issues.
So this step one of the masses that will be displayed right now if you click on the save all now, if
you go to the refresh.
So first of all, that will display consistent display as if they have some issues right out front,
you get the idea how to deal with multiple promises.
OK.
So thanks for watching.
I will see you in the next video.