Hello, friend, welcome back in this video, under-discussed about one of the most important things
are the fetch API.
So that is a phage web API.
OK.
The index to the fetch API, we can get all the data.
We can also able to store this data.
So first of all, I want to do I want to get this data here to have the API as a API and then tap on
of the link for that user.
So that is already met API.
OK.
And here that is all of the user API.
So I want to do unto actually scratch all that user data.
That means this user data to fatty, then I want to visibility in our way.
OK, that means here on the visible light.
So if you want to do that work, then we can do that work with using this fetch.
That is one of the functions of with func this function, we can actually do that very easily.
I show you like that is I want to do and to remove everything.
So forget all that data from our API that is only that user API onto to get it.
So forget all the data now and don't use it on a that basically building function as a fact.
OK.
So you better make it as a fat web that is a fat API.
So now I want to turn to take one of the variable force that is on on a sector I take on and that constant
variable and then into this constant variable I meet doesn't get API.
OK?
I just simply want to take it.
Goodbye.
And now that is another building functionality, although that is a fetch.
I guess there is one of the building function and into this function area here.
I want to do and load our API.
That means that is our API.
OK, so that is one of the building API under the carpet and now I just simply passed it.
You can also get a lot of the fake API.
If you search into the Google, you can get some of that because if I did this on purpose, I'm actually
using it.
That is all the API and this API on the access.
So now if you want to print it, like here on to do with this console.log with this console.log, I
want to do it to print out this gift guide API.
And then what exactly this data will be displayed not going to get save all.
And now if you go and or browser refresh now because it is not past all of the promises, OK, there
is no past one of the promises and also the pending.
So when you get any promises, as I told you before, then we can able to access our two of this methods
to them and then cat, right?
So I want to do on to use it here.
So I with this get it API here to use that as a then matter and in this then matter area, whatever
the response that I would get beat down to make it as a functional area so that I get that response,
that this response data.
Look at this as one that I want to learn to print the Philippines, that it was a console log in with
the console log area here on the pass or distress.
OK, so here I simply pass it over and you already know about this part.
And also, if you want to declare the catch as well, you can also declare that it was a cat.
Right?
That is a catch method.
I already sketched method, but I want to make it into the end of the line.
There is a catch method.
OK.
I remember this catch method I want to do and two percent of their error.
That means if you have any error that will be displayed, this error, that is our functionality.
And here with this console log, with this console.log, I want to display this error.
OK.
I hope you already know about it.
And now if you click on the save all, if you're not going to get the save all, go there to the refresh.
OK, but I want to make it into the year now because it's not past some of the data here that your body
used as a false header color type, you are tell.
So that is one of the response and into this response data that is on the body.
OK, into this body, if you open it now you see on games that are readable, esteemed data.
So here now we have to do you have to access, are these readable and stream all that data?
So if you want to access it, then we have to work in here.
So now on to do I want to get this data.
I want to get all that.
Our user details data right?
If you want to get it, then also to have done the building method as a JSON.
So that is on the JSON that I wanted to call out this JSON.
So right now, we're trying to move it, OK, remove it.
And then I want to call this response to that is a response.
And then just on.
OK.
That is not just a method.
So I simply call it a comment.
And after that, after that here right now, that is all the promises data so we can use and then say,
make it as an adult, then then method and then method area here to pass.
While the parameter, the profile that the user profile or whatever you choose right now make it as
a profile.
And then with our array function here, I want to do either display or this profile that is account
console.log and this console.log area here to parse that profile.
OK?
I simply parsed this profile.
And now if you arrange it, so that is all the JSON data.
So it is just one will get all.
We are able to access all that our this user API.
OK.
So just don't get this data.
That is all I have.
Already taken out of there then, and I just take one of the parameters, the profiles right now, all
the data into this profile.
So now I want to do under-display this profile dataset.
With this console.log, I display this profile.
Now, if you click the save all and now if you go clear the refresh so you can see it's not successfully
now, get all that user data.
OK.
In our API, whatever the data is in here, if you go to our API, that means that our API, you can
see that is all that our API details data.
So now this data is accessible in here.
Okay, because everything is in here.
I hope print, you get some idea how to work with the fast function.
So with this fast function, we are able to get all the data with the JSON method.
And then here it's simply loaded.
OK?
Just simply understand how that functionality work lately will go more deep.
Just simply understand that fetch from output.
OK, so that is the fundamental series, a fundamental series.
You have to just remember what exactly that.
Then the fat just simply remember, it literally will build the project.
Then everything will be more clear.
OK, so how can access that API?
I hope it's very much clear to you.