Hello, friend, welcome back.
You know, previous video I have discussed about that feature.
Yeah.
And here, first of all, we knew Ronnie Dennis actually passed one of the branches, right?
And for the reasons here, when you get that as a promise, then you're going to be able to access that
then and catch right.
So not only do I want to apply the same things with using another functionality that is that I think
carried that we don't need to use that then or the catch one that is here, that same functionality.
OK, that means user that I simply get it with that just on right to the JSON that we get that all the
data.
So that going to do the same things with using another form raped right now.
But I want to do here.
I want to make it as a comment out, OK.
And now here I want to do first of all, I want a picture of the function that is a function.
And here I name, it doesn't get in full form from it.
OK.
Getting from it.
And here I simply declare one of the function.
And when you use that synchrony, then first of all, here we have to do.
We have to add that async run.
OK, that is and see, I think Graham.
And here we have to, first of all, call it and then that will be our function.
And I just put that function name as a gate info.
Far from it.
OK.
In full, I just naming, does it get info from that?
So in particular, that position, first of all, we have to do, we have to call the same things.
We have to get that out.
We have to fetch all that.
Our API so simply pasted took that is our constant variable as a gate API.
And with this guide API, I just simply fact all the data.
OK?
I simply fetch all that data bit and I want to do under displayed so fully displayed and that will be
I take another variable, the constant variable.
I just name it as a profile.
OK, name it does a profile.
So with this profile?
First of all, here we have to do.
We have to get that before I get this data with this then and then our test on method, right?
So now all we have to do, we have to run this JSON.
So I simply copied and here I paste so that with this, that will be actually fetch all that the user
data.
OK, and now when using that as an gurnett, then here all you have to do.
We have to use that.
Our it.
OK, now wait.
So here we have to use it as a function.
So now with this, our function, then that is our JSON map todo till we get all that data, which everything
is right now in our this variable as a profile variable.
Now I want to turn to this play this profile.
That means that with this console, sorry that the console with this console.
So now with this console, log into this console to print out this profile, right?
And to bring this profile here, you can see I didn't use any -- gas.
That is one.
Form it, we can use it rather than you can also use it, OK?
And now that is one of the function right now.
We have to do have to display this functionality from the display that we have to call this.
That is a gate that is our get info from gate, right?
So here I simply call our dysfonctionnement.
Now, if you click on the save all now, if you go click the refresh.
Now serving as the oncogene promise references to friends is not defined preferences.
Here you can see that could be.
Obviously, this names a bit.
I make it as a reference.
OK, so that it with references.
Now if you click on the save all.
And now if you go to the refresh again, there's a gists on there.
There is.
Jason is not a function.
This just on his daughter function.
You can see here.
Also, you have to do into the fat, into the search area here.
Also, we have to parse that out.
OK, so that is allowed on the function and then that is our fetch.
OK.
So here also, we have to add that, as I would add also here, we have to add that out right now.
Let's check this out.
Give you to save all now.
Go directly to the refresh.
Yes, you can see it's done successfully now.
Get all that user data.
OK, who's our followers?
User details everything because the logging details, location issues are all that object is now successfully
gated and now is visible in here.
I offering to give some idea how can work with these promises?
Also, another one of the grown up here.
You can actually do that.
Same things with using that hasn't grown up here.
All you have to do app tap to add that asynchronous element function and then before that fats.
Here you have to call this function as the output and also integrate the data with this JSON from it.
Then here also you have to add our OK, so that is a simple work with using that as in Gurnett.
And then that is all promises that I will produce very much clear to you in your next video and you
start a new session.
It's about the DOM.
Don't be mean, the document object model.
So step by step, I will try to share everything with you.
So thanks for watching.
I will see you in the next video.